Now we are ready to perform our analysis.
现在我们可以进行分析了
The resulting returns time series is
生成的收益率时间序列
the theoretical monthly performance of our long-short portfolio.
理论上是多空投资组合的月度业绩
Our goal is to see if the mean monthly return is greater than zero.
我们的目标是查看平均月度收益率是否大于零
Let's calculate that.
我们来计算下
So, our mean is indeed greater than zero at 0.53 percent,
平均收益率为 0.53% 的确大于零
but does this mean that we got this value because
这个值是否表明
on average this trading strategy yields positive returns?
平均下来这个交易策略能够产生正收益？
That is to say that the true mean is greater than zero?
也就是说真实均值大于零？
It could be that on average this trading strategy will not yield positive returns.
有可能平均下来 这个策略没有产生正收益
Maybe the true mean is less than or equal to zero,
也许真实均值小于或等于零
and this value is just a random fluctuation.
这个值只是随机的波动值
Well, one approach to assess this is to perform a statistical test on our hypothesis.
一种评估方法是对假设进行统计学检验
A t-test is a way of testing the probability of getting as bigger mean as we did,
T 检验可以检验获得与我们所得均值一样大的概率
assuming all the assumptions we made to build our model of strategy returns were correct.
假设我们构建策略收益率模型的所有假设都正确
In our case, we can compute the t-statistic by dividing
对我们来说 计算 t 统计量的方法是
the mean return x bar by the standard error of the mean SE x bar.
用均值收益率 ((x) 除以均值的标准差 (SE (x)
Using this t-statistic, we can measure the probability
我们可以使用该 t 统计量衡量
of getting a mean monthly return of 0.53 percent or
如果真实平均月度收益率是零
larger if the true mean monthly return is
获得的平均月度收益率为 0.53% 或更高的概率是多少
zero given that the assumptions we made to build our model are correct.
假设构建模型时做出的所有假设都正确
This probability is called the p-value.
这个概率称为 p 值
If the probability is very small,
如果这个概率很小
we might infer that it's unlikely that the true mean is zero.
那么可以推断真实均值不太可能为零
Now, before running the test,
在进行检验之前
we should decide how small the p-value needs to
我们需要决定 p 值多小
be for us to conclude that the true mean is not zero.
才能推断真实均值不是零
To denote this threshold,
我们通常用希腊字母 α
we usually use the Greek symbol alpha.
表示这个阈值
A commonly used value is 0.1.
常用值为 0.1
Setting alpha sets the false positive rate for the test.
设置 α 就设定了检验的假正例率
So, if we set alpha equals 0.1,
如果 α 等于 0.1
we're effectively saying that if we use this threshold,
就相当于如果使用这个阈值的话
we are incorrectly rejecting the null hypothesis when the true mean
当真实均值在 10% 的假设检验情形下为零时
is zero in 10 percent of many hypothetical users of this test.
我们能够接受拒绝这种零假设
By performing a one-tail t-test on
通过对
the alternative hypothesis that the mean of
这些收益率的均值在统计学上大于零
these returns is statistically greater than zero,
这一备择假设执行单尾 t 检验
we calculate the p-value with
我们使用自由度 n-1 = 47
the stats package using a degrees of freedom of n minus one equals 47,
计算出统计包的 p 值
and we find that the t-statistic is about 1.618,
得出 t 统计量约为 1.618
with the p-value of 0.0566.
p 值为 0.0566
Meaning that the result is not significant at P less than 0.05 level,
表明在 p &lt; 0.05 时结果不具显著性
but insignificant at P less than 0.1.
但是在 p &lt; 0.1 时具有显著性
This means that we are fairly unlikely to get a mean of
这就表示如果真实均值为零
0.53 percent if the true mean is zero.
我们不太可能获得均值 0.53%
This result shows some initial promise
这个结果初始证明了
that there could be some alpha contained in the strategy,
策略中可能包含 alpha 信号
and thus serves as a quick sanity check to justify investigating further and
可以作为快速健全性检查以证明可以进一步调查
fine-tuning the strategy leading to a full backtesting exercise in the end.
并且细调策略 最终执行完整的回溯测试任务
If we measure the monthly performance of the SPDR,
如果衡量标普 500 ETF
S&amp;P 500 ETF, SPY over the same period,
在同一时期的月度业绩
we would find that the mean monthly return is 0.83 percent,
我们发现平均月度收益率是 0.83%
which is actually greater than that of the strategy,
实际上大于我们的策略得出的结果
at least at this preliminary stage.
至少在这一初始阶段是这样
To be clear, comparing our momentum strategy to the strategy of
澄清下 将我们的动量策略与
investing directly in S&amp;P 500 ETF is not really a fair comparison.
直接投资标普 500 ETF 进行比较并不公平
These are two very different strategies.
这两个策略差别很大
For one thing, ours involves taking long and short positions,
首先 我们的策略包含多头和空头股票
while investing in the S&amp;P only involves taking long positions.
而投资标普 500 只有多头
However, this gives us a vague idea of what values portfolio returns might take.
但是 可以大致告诉我们投资组合收益率可能是什么样的值
Also, while our strategy's obviously simplistic to begin with,
并且 我们的策略很明显比较简单
this shows that it is actually not
表明实际上
an easy task to find a strategy that can outperform the market.
很难找到一个跑赢大盘的策略
Note that if you get a very large p-value at this early stage,
注意 如果在初期得出很大的 p 值
you wouldn't want to go back and make meaningless changes to
则不建议对策略做出无意义的更改
your strategy like changing a parameter a little until you got a very low p-value.
例如小幅更改某个参数 直到 p 值很低
Doing this is called data snooping or p-hacking,
这种做法称为数据窥视或 p 值操控
and would just fine tune your strategy to exploit
这么做只是细调策略
the particular random fluctuations in the dataset you have.
使其能利用数据集中存在的随机波动情况
A strategy device that way would be unlikely to perform well on future data.
通过这种方式制定的策略在未来数据上不太可能表现得好
What you should do instead is make meaningful changes to your strategy.
你应该对策略做出有意义的更改
In other words, you should come up with
换句话说 你应该想出其他策略
a different idea for a strategy and test that instead.
并对其进行检验